how's it going everyone typically
five-year with a very excessive beer
today and this video is dedicated to
some very stupid who decide to
give me me hate for one of my last
videos more specifically the goAnimate
video people have been saying that is
cheap I'm being lazy with no I'm not
I found a cool animating software
this is why different than you I'm
different when you look at it you think
this is this from cheap free soft OH
software when I look at it I think damn
I can make some Sonic Underground videos
with this do you get what I'm
putting down
do you understand no you don't cuz
you're you're my pitches are you
picking up what I'm putting down
you better be you better cuz I mean
do you get one thing nobody gave me hey
formats drugs all video I made three
years ago that was the coolest
thing ever
oh my God I'll make a video fella a cool
hip dance party and you gotta say it
Plus ass no no we don't look like that
me beating your ass now that was I mean
I'm watching you you fitted me you
understand when I mix all your videos I
want to make them cuz it's hard it's
pause you make talk on the Bell videos
you can't help you with that
stupid ass stupid ass myself in
this saying that minute
if this cold guy if it can this to
about cougar we build a mini T so
making other videos with some free
animation software you calling him lazy
you come meet me I'd say more evil
five look at my username
look down that and tell me what my
username press does that work does it
not say Tim annoys people files going
through my you tell and read my head up
what does it say the home of Sonic
Underground can you not read is it
that help we are you are are your baby
you can read it I don't know what
say all the bags I'm the key Mexico
because I love it you Shawn is going to
rap Sonic Underground that's the
that is the anyway next video will
be up next week
trust me this is one video you have been
waiting a while for and when it comes
out your girl love this